[{"question": " okay, pick a card, any card.  all right, now memorize it. show to everybody. got it?", "answer": " um-mm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " real magic does exist.", "answer": " wow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " wow. joey,  how do you do it?", "answer": " i can\u0092t tell you that, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " ah, somebody\u0092s at the door on the ceiling.", "answer": " noo, that\u0092s our unbelievably loud upstairs neighbor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " he took up the carpet, and now you can hear everything.", "answer": " why don\u0092t you go up there and ask him to \u0091step lightly, please?\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i have like five times, but the guy is so charming, that i go up there to yell and then i end up apologizing to him.", "answer": " ooh, that is silly.  i\u0092ll go up there, i\u0092ll tell him to keep it down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " all right, be my guest.", "answer": " good luck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  yeah, look i was with my friend downstairs and we hear everything up here that you do, and i am sick and tired... .", "answer": "  whoa, you are very beautiful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  hey, anybody got a length of rope about six feet long with a little nouse at the end?", "answer": " honey, what\u0092s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i just saw janice.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, she was at rockefeller center skating with her husband, she looked so happy. i almost feel bad for whipping that kid\u0092s pretzel at them.", "answer": " man, i remember the first time i saw that girl katherine, after we broke up. she was just walking with her friend donna, just laughing and talking. god, it killed me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yes, but you ended up having sex with both of them that afternoon.", "answer": " sorry, i just, any excuse to tell that story y'know....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey chandler, there\u0092s a party tomorrow, you\u0092ll feel better then.", "answer": " oh, y'know what, i\u0092m gonna be okay, you don\u0092t have to throw a party for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " it\u0092s joey\u0092s birthday.", "answer": " oh, well then, if anybody should have a party it should be him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  how\u0092s that coffee comin,\u0092 dear?", "answer": "  yeah, right away mr. kaplan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i\u0092m not supposed to drink coffee, it makes me gassy.", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " i\u0092ll bet your thinking, \u0091what\u0092s an intelligent girl who wants to be in fashion, doing making coffee?\u0092 eh?", "answer": " op.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " eh.", "answer": " oh, you got me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " well, don\u0092t think i haven\u0092t noticed your potential. well, i\u0092ve got a project for you that\u0092s a lot more related to fashion. how does that sound?", "answer": " oh, that sounds great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh thank you so much mr. kaplan, thank you so much.", "answer": "  i need these hangers separated asap.  you\u0092re welcome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh god, i hate my job, i hate it, i hate my job, i hate it.", "answer": " i know honey, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh, i wanna quit, but then i think i should stick it out, then i think why would such a person stay in such a demeaning job, just because it\u0092s remotely related to the field they\u0092re interested in.", "answer": "  gee, i don\u0092t know rach. order up!! i got a yentel soup, a james beans, and a howdy hold the dowdy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  hi! is my misery amusing to you?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i wa, i wa, i was just ah....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " it\u0092s not funny, this is actually my job.", "answer": " oh believe me, i-i-i\u0092ve been there. i had to sort mannequin heads at that mannequins plus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh well then, so i\u0092m just going to go back to talking to my friend here. and you can go back to enjoying your little hamburger.", "answer": " ah, just one other thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " yes?!", "answer": " i ah, i work at bloomingdale\u0092s and i might know of a job possibility if your, if your interested?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  hey guys.", "answer": " hey gunther. hi.  i mean you\u0092re going out on a date with the noisy guy upstairs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " well, he\u0092s very charming.", "answer": " i know, he\u0092s too charming, but if you two start going out, then it\u0092s just gonna make it so much harder for me to hate him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " well, you\u0092re just gonna have to try.", "answer": " joey, where are the jello shots?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " chandler!", "answer": " hello-dillillio!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh, somebody\u0092s feeling better.", "answer": "  stick out your tongue.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh my!!", "answer": " oh my god! how many of these things did you have? these are pure vodka.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah, jello just like mom used to make.", "answer": "  the most unbelievable thing happened to me today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi! so i\u0092m out having lunch at monica\u0092s and this guy starts talking to me, and it turns out he works for a buyer at bloomingdale\u0092s and there happens to be an opening in his department. so i gave him my phone number and he\u0092s gonna call me this weekend to see if he can get me an interview!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " what, so this guy is helping you for no apparent reason?", "answer": " uh-huh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " and he\u0092s, he\u0092s a total stranger?", "answer": " yeah! his name is um, mark something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " huh. sounds like mark something wants to have some sex.", "answer": " what!?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m just saying, i mean why else would he just, y'know, swoop in out of nowhere for no reason.", "answer": " to be nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " hey, joey. are men ever nice to strange women for no reason?", "answer": " no, only for sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " thank you.  so did you ah, did you tell mark something about me?", "answer": " i didn\u0092t have to, because i was wearing my \u0091i heart ross\u0092 sandwich board and ringing my bell.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": "  joey!!! happy birthday!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey!! hey-hey-hey!", "answer": "  okay, how many of that girl are you seeing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " how hammered are you? huh? these, these are joey\u0092s sisters.", "answer": " hi joey\u0092s sisters!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey. what are we drinkin\u0092 over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " well, i have ah, vodka and cranberry juice.", "answer": " no kiddin,\u0092 that\u0092s the exact same drink i made myself right after i shot my husband.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  what \u0091cha doing?", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m taking my ex-girlfriend of my speed dialer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " oh!!", "answer": " no-no-no-no, no, it\u0092s a good thing. why must we dial so speedily anyway? why must we rush through life? why can\u0092t we savor the precious moments?  those are some huge breasts you have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah. so um, i-i heard about this ah, mark guy that ah, rachel met today.", "answer": " isn\u0092t that great?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh yeah! so ah, kinda pretty, pretty good. he sounds like a nice, good guy.", "answer": " oh, he is. and he is so dreamy. i mean, y'know what, when he left i actually used the phrase, \u0091hummina-hummina-hummina.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  so, he\u0092s just a nice guy. you really think this mark doesn\u0092t want anything in exchange for helping him?", "answer": " well, i assume i\u0092ll have to take showers with him, but y'know, that\u0092s true of any job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " how ya feelin\u0092?", "answer": " well, my apartment isn\u0092t there anymore, because i drank it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " where\u0092d you get too? we lost you after you opened up all the presents.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yeah, i ended up in the storage room, and not alone.", "answer": " woooo hoooo!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " ow, no \u0091woo-hooing,\u0092 no \u0091woo-hooing.\u0092", "answer": " why, what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " ah, i fooled around with joey\u0092s sister.  well, that\u0092s not the worst part.", "answer": " what is the worse part?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i can\u0092t remember which sister.", "answer": "  you see what men do! don\u0092t tell me men are not nice!  this is men!! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " are you insane? i mean joey, is going to kill you, he\u0092s actually going to kill you dead.", "answer": " okay! you don\u0092t think i thought of that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " how can you not know which one?", "answer": " i mean that\u0092s unbelievable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i mean, was it gina?", "answer": " which one is gina?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " dark, big hair, with the airplane earrings.", "answer": " no, no, no, that\u0092s dina.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  you see you can\u0092t tell which one is which either, dwha!!", "answer": " we didn\u0092t fool around with any of them. dwha! dwha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " veronica. look, it\u0092s got to be veronica, the girl in the red skirt. i definitely stuck my tongue down her throat.", "answer": " that was me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " look, when i\u0092ve been drinking, sometimes i tend to get overly friendly, and i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " that\u0092s all right.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  can i talk to you for a second?!", "answer": " hey, joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " why can\u0092t we talk in here? with, with, witnesses.", "answer": " i just got off the phone with my sister.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " ah, which, which one?", "answer": " mary-angela.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " mary-angela.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " y'know which one was she again?", "answer": " why don\u0092t you ask chandler, \u0091cause he\u0092s the one that fooled around with her. she told me you said you could really fall for her. now is that true? or are you just gettin\u0092 over janice by groping my sister.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " it\u0092s gotta be the first one.", "answer": " really? that\u0092s great! you and my sister, sittin\u0092 in a tree.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " did he call? did mark call?", "answer": " no honey, i\u0092m sorry, but the weekend\u0092s not over yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh.  oh my god, is that phoebe?", "answer": " i guess they\u0092re back from their date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " so, how are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh yeah, what\u0092s it about?", "answer": " i don\u0092t remember. do you wanna take a walk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " dear mary-angela. hi. how\u0092s it going. this is the hardest letter i\u0092ve ever had to write.  what the hell\u0092s a matter with you? how do you think joey\u0092s going to react when he finds out that you blew off his sister with a letter?", "answer": " well, that\u0092s the part where you tell him that i moved to france. when actually i\u0092ll be in cuba.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " all right, look, look, you\u0092ve got to do this yourself, okay in person. at least you know her name. you just go to the house and you ask for mary-angela, okay, when which ever one she is comes to the door, you take her for a walk, you let her down easy.", "answer": " what if mary-angela comes to the door and i ask for mary-angela?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  joey, what-wh-wh-wha-wh-wha-wh-wha-wh-wha-what are you doing here?", "answer": " waiting for my grandma to finish my laundry. what about you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i\u0092m here to see mary-angela.", "answer": " you are so the man!  now look, listen, listen, you got to be cool, \u0091cause my grandma doesn\u0092t know about you two yet, and you do not want to tick her off. she was like the sixth person to spit on mussolini's hanging body. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " where\u0092s mary-angela?", "answer": " she\u0092s right in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe mark didn\u0092t call. it\u0092s sunday night, and he didn\u0092t call.", "answer": " bummer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  yeah, right. look at you, you\u0092re practically giddy.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m genuinely sorry the mark thing didn\u0092t work out. look, rach, i want only good things for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " wait a minute, why don\u0092t you just call mark.  i mean, who says you have to sit here and wait for him, you\u0092ve got to make stuff happen.", "answer": " but, you, you don\u0092t want to seem too pushy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  honey, it\u0092s not pushy, he gave her his home number.", "answer": "  what, he gave you his home number? as in like, to, to his home?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yeah, and you don\u0092t mind if i call, because you only want good things for me.", "answer": " that\u0092s right good things, that-that is what i said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "  hello, mark? hi, it\u0092s rachel green.  oh no, don\u0092t you apologize.  yeah, i\u0092ll hold.  he left my number at work, but he was helping his niece with her report on the pioneers.", "answer": " that is so made up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  yeah, oh my god, tomorrow! that, no, it\u0092s perfect. oh god, thank you soo much. great! bye!  i got the interview!", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " there you go.", "answer": " he even offered to meet me for lunch tomorrow to prep me for it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " oh, that is amazing!", "answer": " yeah well, if i know mark, and i think i do, i\u0092d expect nothing less.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i got to figure out what i\u0092m going to wear.", "answer": " high collar and baggy pants say i\u0092m a pro.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " yeah! right! okay, i\u0092ll see you guys later.  woo hoo!", "answer": " you go get \u0091em.  what did i do to you? did i hurt you in some way?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " \u0091why don\u0092t you call him?!\u0092 well, thank you very much! y'know now he is going to prep her, y'know prep her, as in what you do when you surgically remove the boyfriend!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " are you crazy?!", "answer": " am i! am i! am i out of my mind! am i losing my senses!! this dreamy guy is taking my girlfriend out for a meal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " what?! ross y'know this isn\u0092t even about you! i mean this is about rachel and something wonderful happening for her. i mean you know even if you\u0092re right, what if he wants to sleep with her, does it mean he gets too?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i mean don\u0092t you trust her?", "answer": " well, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " then get over yourself! grow up!", "answer": "  you grow up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " this teramisu is, is excellent. did you make it mary-angela?", "answer": " no! i did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " well, it\u0092s, it\u0092s yummy. so mary-angela do you like it?", "answer": " of course! it\u0092s her favorite.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " so um, mary-angela, what\u0092s your second favorite?", "answer": " more of grandma\u0092s teramisu.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " would you just please....give me the receipt \u0091cause this is great. it\u0092s top notch.", "answer": " that dies with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " so will i.", "answer": " excuse yourself, and go to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " oh no-no-no i was just squinting. that doesn\u0092t mean anything.", "answer": "  just do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " finally, i thought we\u0092d never be alone. can i just tell you something, i have not stopped thinking about you since the party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " look, i may have jumped the gun here.  um, i just got out of a relationship and i\u0092m not really in a, in a commitment kind of place.", "answer": " so! me neither! god, mary-angela was right you do have the softest lips.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " ahhhh, you\u0092re not mary-angela.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m mary-theresa.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " this is so bad. if-if you\u0092re not mary-angela, then-then who is?", "answer": "  i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " joey!!!", "answer": " no joey! no joey! don\u0092t joey! joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " what\u0092s goin\u0092 on?", "answer": "  you\u0092re it! now run and hide!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " it\u0092s no big deal. chandler was just kissin\u0092 me because he thought i was mary-angela.", "answer": " what?! how could you do that, how could you think she was mary-angela?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " i wasn\u0092t sure which one mary-angela was.  look, i\u0092m sorry okay, i was really drunk, and you all look really similar.", "answer": " i say, punch him joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " yeah! punch him!!", "answer": " y'know what, we should all calm down because your brother\u0092s not going to punch me.  are ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " well, that is usually what i would do. but i just never thought you\u0092d be on the receiving end of it. how could you do this?!", "answer": " joey if you wanna punch me, go ahead, i deserve it. but i just want you to know that i would never soberly hurt you or your family, you\u0092re my best friend. i would never do anything like this ever again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " so what. i say, punch him.", "answer": " yeah! punch him! punch him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " no! no! no! no, i\u0092m not going to punch chandler.", "answer": " i\u0092ll do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " no you won\u0092t. look he knows he did a terrible thing and i believe him, he\u0092s sorry. but,  you\u0092ve got one more apology to make, all right, you\u0092ve got to apologize to mary-angela.", "answer": " okay, absolutely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " you\u0092ve got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " cookie, now you can punch him!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " what are you doing here?", "answer": " ah y'know, this building is on my paper route so i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " how\u0092d did it go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh well, the woman i interviewed with was pretty tough, but y'know thank god mark coached me, because once i started talking about the fall line, she got all happy and wouldn\u0092t shut up.", "answer": " i\u0092m so proud of you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " me too!", "answer": " listen, i\u0092m ah, i\u0092m sorry i\u0092ve been so crazy and jealous and, it\u0092s just that i like you a lot, so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " yeah.  hi mark!", "answer": " hi. i just talked to joanna, and she loves you. you got it, you got the job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " oh, i did!", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " so ah, phoebe, how was your date?", "answer": " oh well y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " yeah, i do know.", "answer": " ick, you were eavesdropping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " eavesdropping. pheebs, the ceiling tiles were falling down.", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m sorry. but i really like this guy. and i think he really happens to like me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " maybe the pogo-stick likes it too?", "answer": " all right, that\u0092s it! he cannot do this to phoebe.  this guy is going to get the butt kicking of a lifetime!  but, is he a big guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " thanks you guys! thank you.", "answer": " don\u0092t worry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " god, i hope they kick his ass!", "answer": " honey, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}]